# Ivan Darijenko

Odessa, Ukraine



dariienko555@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ivan-dariienko-941341289/

## **Summary**

I'm Ivan, a senior software engineer with over 6 years of experience in software engineering & web development.

I'm highly organized, self- motivated, and proficient with both frontend & backend technologies. I'm seeking to use my hard won technical and programming skills alongside proven project management to improve quality, cost and time metrics for web application development.

I am a great communicator, enjoy collaborating within teams where I bring my creativity in problem solving, drive and efficiency to the table. I believe in being a self-starter, thinking critically and taking accountability for my work and responsibilities, while inspiring the same in people around me.

#### **Experience**



#### No-code Developer

Drop Center, Expertuity

Sep 2023 - Present

- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to gather and analyze business requirements for complex projects.
- Optimized database structures and implemented robust data management solutions.

## No-code Developer

Clause Out

Nov 2021 - Apr 2023 (1 year 6 months)

- Led the development of comprehensive web applications using Bubble.io, Airtable, Webflow, Zapier and Retool.
- Mentored junior developers and contributed to continuous improvement initiatives.
- Managed the entire software development life cycle from requirement gathering to design, development, testing, and implementation.



#### **No-code Developer**

Dropmed

Sep 2020 - Jul 2021 (11 months)

- Developed and maintained multiple web applications using Bubble.io, Airtable, and Webflow.
- Implemented custom workflows using Zapier for seamless process automation.
- Collaborated closely with clients to understand and address their unique business needs.
- Ensured high performance and reliability of applications.



#### **No-Code Developer**

#### Revvo

Nov 2019 - Aug 2020 (10 months)

- Employed by this esteemed organization for almost 10 months as a bubble developer.
- Played a key role in the development and enhancement of web applications using Bubble.io and Airtable.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to gather and analyze business requirements.
- Implemented user interfaces and workflows to improve overall user experience
- Gained extensive knowledge of API calls.
- Built scalable systems capable of handling vast amounts of data in designing and integrating APIs



#### 👩 Full Stack Developer Intern

#### AppRecode

Sep 2018 - Oct 2019 (1 year 2 months)

- Developed and maintained front-end and back-end components of web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Node.js and PHP.
- Assisted in database design and management.
- Gained hands-on experience in full-stack development and contributed to the overall project life cycle.

#### Education



### Sumy State University

Bachelor, Computer Science Sep 2014 - Jul 2018

#### **Skills**

- Bubble.io
- JavaScript
- Amazon Web Services (AWS)
- Flask
- Django
- Ruby on Rails
- DevOps
- Laravel
- Responsive Design
- No-Code Development
- Low-Code Development
- Webflow

- Airtable
- Retool
- Zapier
- API
- Progressive Web App
- Python
- Machine Learning
- Web Scrapping
- React
- Vue
- Typescript
- Angular